

abdulkareem.fallaha.mnv@gmail. com

+963 96 917 3279

0

Aleppo, Syria

abdulkareem-fallaha.me

in

linkedin.com/in/abdulkareemfallaha-241068137



aboood.asq

SKILLS

PHP

Bootstrap

Java

Semantic UI



wordpress

Tailwind.css

MySQL

Codelgniter

Python

Web Development

Project Management

Technical Documentation

LANGUAGES

English



















Abdulkareem Fallaha

Full Stack Web Developer

Experienced Web Specialist and Quality Assurance Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Full Stack Web Development. Strong media and communication professional who graduated from the University of Aleppo, Informatics Faculty.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Quality Assurance

Automata4 Group

08/2015 - 07/2018Aleppo , Syria

Automata4 Group is a Syria-based company dedicated to providing high quality customg IT solutions and Consulting services

Full Stack Developer

CLIC Agency

08/2018 - 01/2019 Damascus, Syria

CLIC is a marketing and branding agency. From branding, web design and development to social media to social media, marketing strategies, planning

Full Stack Developer

GivingLoop

02/2019 - Present Amman, Jordan

GivingLoop aims to disrupt how nonprofits raise funds and become sustainable. https://www.givingloop.org/

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Laravel Builder (07/2017 - Present)

Website that gives programmers tools to build websites with laravel back-end, Bootstrap front-end

Al-Bakkar Trading Company (10/2018 - 12/2018)

Website for Al-Bakkar Trading Company. www.bakkar-trd.com

Syrian Society for Scientific Research (09/2019 - Present)

□ Building the website of the SySSR (http://website.syssr.org) & Managing the CMS for the SySSr

EDUCATION

Information Technology University of Aleppo

10/2012 - 04/2018 Aleppo, Syria - GPA (77.9)

Master Web Science Syrian Virtual University

05/2018 - Present

Aleppo . Svria

CERTIFICATES

Bachelor of Technology - BTech GPA (77.9) (10/2012 - 05/2018)

ACHIEVEMENTS

Full Stack Development workshop at Informatics Faculty (02/2019 - 02/2019)

Workshop in web development at Informatics Faculty, Key Words: (HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP)

Full Stack Development workshop at Syria Trust (Shabab Aleppo) (03/2019 - 03/2019)

Workshop in web development at Syria Trust (Shabab Aleppo), Key Words: (HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP)

Full Stack Development workshop at Syria Trust (Shabab Aleppo) (10/2019 - 11/2019) Workshop in web development at Syria Trust (Shabab Aleppo), Key Words: (SEO, Bootstrap, JavaScript, PHP, MVC, git)